Map<String, dynamic> json = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who's the first to die in DBZ?",
      "anwsers": ["Raditz", "Farmer", "Nappa", "Goku"],
      "correct": "Farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's Goku biggest fear?",
      "anwsers": ["Losing", "Chichi", "Needles", "Vegeta"],
      "correct": "Needles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the acual names of the Androids 17 and 18?",
      "anwsers": ["Lapis and Lazuli", "Aqua and Magma", "Beta and Omega", "Robert and Samantha"],
      "correct": "Lapis and Lazuli"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the latest Dragon Ball game?",
      "anwsers": [
        "Dragon Ball FighterZ",
        "Dragon Ball Kakarot",
        "Dragon Ball Heroes: World Mission",
        "Dragon Ball The Breakers"
      ],
      "correct": "Dragon Ball The Breakers"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which form of Majin Buu is the strongest?",
      "anwsers": ["Kid Buu", "Super Buu", "Super Buuhan", "Majin Buu"],
      "correct": "Super Buuhan"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many World Martial Arts Tournament Goku has won?",
      "anwsers": ["0", "1", "3", "4"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tien fought all the major Dragon Ball Z Vilains, except for one. Who's it?",
      "anwsers": ["Majin Buu", "Cell", "The Saiyans", "Frieza"],
      "correct": "Frieza"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many episodes there are in Dragon Ball GT?",
      "anwsers": ["60", "62", "64", "70"],
      "correct": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the major reason for Frieza to destroying the Planet Vegeta?",
      "anwsers": [
        "Get rid of the saiyans",
        "Beerus ordered him to do it",
        "Being the strongest in the universe",
        "He was scared of the Super Saiyan"
      ],
      "correct": "Beerus ordered him to do it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many times did Goku has died so far?",
      "anwsers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is a game where Naruto wears Goku's clothes, which game is it?",
      "anwsers": [
        "Naruto Ultimate Ninja 3",
        "Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja 5",
        "Naruto: Shinobi Retsuden",
        "Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja Storm 3"
      ],
      "correct": "Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja Storm 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the maximum Kaioken multiplier so far?",
      "anwsers": ["Kaioken X5", "Kaioken X10", "Kaioken X20", "Kaioken X50"],
      "correct": "Kaioken X20"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Android is the most powerful currently?",
      "anwsers": ["Android 16", "Android 17", "Android 18", "Cell Max"],
      "correct": "Cell Max"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was Goku first major enemy?",
      "anwsers": ["Pilaf", "Demon King Piccolo", "Tao Pai Pai", "Raditz"],
      "correct": "Pilaf"
    },
  ]
};
